<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ㅇㅁㅈ</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ㅇㅁㅈ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Basics: Regular Expressions</title>
      <link>/posts/python-basics-control-flow-and-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/python-basics-control-flow-and-functions/</guid>
      <description>#Run the following code in order to use python on RStudio
x = &amp;#39;hello world&amp;#39; print(x) ## hello world #The following presents with several real-world strings. The task is to use regular expressions in python to match (and return) the requested parts in each
#Using re.findall(), match all numbers and pull them from the following string (string1).
import re string1=&amp;quot;We have to extract these numbers 12, 47, 48 The integers numbers are also interesting: 189 2036 314\&amp;#39;,\&amp;#39; is a separator, so please extract these numbers 125,789,1450 and also these 564,90456 We like to offer you 7890$ per month in order to complete this task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Wrangling and Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/projects/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project1/</guid>
      <description>Data Wrangling and Data Exploration Andrew Lee ml45932
##0 Introduction getwd() ## [1] &amp;quot;/Users/andrewminjolee/Desktop/website3/content/Projects&amp;quot; performance&amp;lt;-read.csv(&amp;quot;exam.csv&amp;quot;,TRUE,&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;) medicalcost&amp;lt;-read.csv(&amp;quot;insurance.csv&amp;quot;,TRUE,&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;) The first dataset is about student performance in three different(subjects) exams along with parental education level and completion of test preparation. The second dataset is about individual’s medical cost charged by healthcare insurance companies. As I’m interested in healthcare and medicine, I’d like to know if there is any interesting relationship between student’s performance and the cost of insurance with consideration of factors like economic, personal, and social.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About ㅇㅁㅈ</title>
      <link>/about-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! My name is Min Jo Lee or Andrew; either works! I study Computational Biology and Business Healthcare at the University of Texas at Austin. I&#39;m currently learning how to incorporate knowledge and skills of Data Science into Healthcare and Medicine. Other than academic work, I play or watch soccer and enjoy cooking. Sometimes I write film reviews.
 📄 🏆 🔬 🇰🇷 Thanks for dropping by and feel free to contact via **andrewminjolee@gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Modeling</title>
      <link>/projects/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/project2/</guid>
      <description>##Min Jo (Andrew) Lee ml45932
data(package = .packages(all.available = TRUE)) #0. (5 pts) Introduce your dataset and each of your variables (or just your main variables if you have lots) in a paragraph.
getwd() ## [1] &amp;quot;/Users/andrewminjolee/Desktop/website3/content/Projects&amp;quot; heart&amp;lt;-read.csv(&amp;quot;heart.csv&amp;quot;,TRUE,&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;) head(heart,10) ## age sex cp trestbps chol fbs restecg thalach exang oldpeak slope ca thal target ## 1 63 1 3 145 233 1 0 150 0 2.3 0 0 1 1 ## 2 37 1 2 130 250 0 1 187 0 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examining the Effects of I100S of CDHR3 Solubility in E.coli</title>
      <link>/projects/examining-the-effects-of-i100s-of-cdhr3-solubility-in-e.coli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/examining-the-effects-of-i100s-of-cdhr3-solubility-in-e.coli/</guid>
      <description>Abstract
Human rhinovirus is a virus that causes common cold illnesses. Rhinovirus C (RV-C), one of the three genetically distinct groups of rhinovirus, is mainly responsible for deadly illnesses such as asthma. On a molecular level, the expression of human protein Cadherin-related facility member (CDHR3), more specifically, its structural domain 1 and 2 are thought to be the binding sites for RV-C that is then introduced in our body. To determine the protein structure and its mechanism, purification can be done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>